Kinme Cleaning
Stain removal is essentially
all about chemistry.
Apply the correct solutions to the layers
of the stain in the right order...
Wow!
And see? That's how you can
completely remove a stain.
Wow!
Amazing!
Question! Where do you buy
the detergents that you use?
I always buy them from a salesman
who comes to visit once a week.
Question!
Does he have to come here in person?
Can't you buy them online instead?
Huh? Oh, well...
I believe I've heard that you can,
but I don't know how to use the internet.
Oh. Um...
You really don't know
how to use the internet?
Wash It
All Away
Episode 7   You Should Leverage Your Assets!!
Thank you for taking time out of
your busy schedule to see us today!
Are you sure this wasn't
too much of a distraction?
Not at all. You caught me
right when work was slow,
and I'm happy to help out
with your summer research projects.
Nairo-chan is always studying.
Mm-hmm.
Yes! I love to study things!
Nairo-chan's grandmother sent
these over as a gift. They're so good!
Little top snails. They're kind of crunchy
but still tender and so creamy!
Come in!
Hello, Sumiyaki-san!
Hi, Kinme-san. It's nice to see you again.
May I ask you to wait here
for just a moment?
Sure.
Sorry, girls. The salesman arrived,
so please wait in here, okay?
The salesman is here?
My apologies! Thank you for waiting.
Not at all.
I've brought you the latest catalog.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I'm running out of
plastic garment bags.
Could I order some more?
Sure. I'll put you down for some.
By the way, Kinme-san, do you use social
media or text messaging for your business?
Huh? Social...?
A kind of online advertising.
Oh, I see. On-line...?
Take a look at this.
Kamasu Sales, Ltd.
This is our company's Facenote account.
Kamasu
Kamasu Sales, Ltd.
We also have a website and
distribute advertisements via text.
We bring quality merchandise to individual customers
as well as hotels, inns, and restaurants.
Please inquire about wholesale and large orders.
We respond promptly and professionally.
Call
Send Message
Follow
Home  Posts  Reviews  Pictures  Videos  Community
Basic Info
Huh.
Category
Wholesale / Supply Store
Address
______ 4-5-6, Atami, Shizuoka Prefecture
I wonder if I actually
need something like that, though.
Oh, you really can't get by
without it these days.
National Cleaning Newspaper
Scenes from the Cleaning Industry
The trade papers are full of
articles talking about it.
In today's world, everyone knows it's best
to attract new customers online.
Oh.
If you rely on old-school
snail mail and flyers,
you'll end up severely
limiting your reach.
Um...
Besides clothes, don't you clean other
kinds of leather and fabric items too?
Uh, yes.
Speaking of which, didn't you recently
wash a fishing banner and doll?
I hear your customers were very pleased.
W-Well, I try to do my best.
Kinme-san, as a small business,
you're able to bring a personal touch
and great care to your stain removal work.
On top of that, you're blessed with
a fine personality and the looks to match!
You should get online so you can
draw more attention to those qualities
and really start to leverage your assets!
I think if you leverage
those assets better,
it will immediately put you on track
for massive new customer growth!
I'm just not very good
with the internet to begin with.
I know! Why don't you let me handle that?
Huh? Nairo-chan?
My friends and I can
help you with the net.
What?
My, what darling little
supporters you have.
I'm Sumiyaki from sales.
I'm Katakuchi Nairo from Kinomiya
Elementary School, third grade.
I'm her classmate Mebaru Kiito.
I'm Kasago Tao.
Very pleased to meet you all.
But help out? How?
Kii-chan knows a lot about the internet,
so I think she can help you set up
a social media account.
Right?
Mm-hmm!
And I'll take promotional pictures
of you hard at work, Kinme-oneesan,
as your in-house cameraman!
Huh?
But I'm not sure if I should
make you do all that for me.
Why not? You might be
surprised by the results.
Also, school girls teaming up
with a cleaning shop lady
sounds like a really unique crossover!
It doesn't take much to get started,
so why not at least give it a shot?
Hmm. I do usually start to get
fewer drop-offs around this time of year.
I don't know if it'll
make a big difference,
but maybe I will give it a shot.
Mm-hmm!
I'll talk to your parents,
and as long as they say it's okay,
would you be willing
to lend me your expertise?
Sure!
Oh, just be careful not to take
any pictures of my face, okay?
Understood.
You can count on Nairo!
Kinme Cleaning
I shall now begin
taking photos of you at work!
All right! I am in your capable hands.
Okay, without hesitation.
Huh?
I really don't want any pictures
of my face, though.
Understood! I'm sorry.
Hey! I don't think
we need pictures like that.
Candid shots are an absolute
necessity on social media!
Um, I have to go out
and make deliveries now,
so maybe we should call it a day.
Deliveries?! On the contrary, that would
be the perfect photo opportunity!
I will go with you!
Huh?!
We'll be waiting here, okay?
I have a great idea!
Just like that, Kinme-oneesan!
You're perfect!
I-Is this sort of thing
really that eye-catching?
Yes! This is how everyone
on social media does it.
With the castle in frame, it's perfect!
Men's Bath
Women's Bath
Today was a little overwhelming.
Once Nairo-chan gets started on
something, there's no stopping her.
Oh. Good evening!
Here you are again!
Nairo-chan?
Please stay right there!
I'll go get my camera!
Huh? I-I don't need any pictures
of me in the bath!
Kinme Cleaning
It actually looks professionally made!
For all of your precious
garments and accessories
You can count
on Kinme.
Kinme Cleaning
Didn't Kii-chan do great?
Well, Nairo-chan and Tao-chan did good
work on the photo editing and copy too.
Call
Send Message
Follow
Hmm? What's this?
Home  Posts  Reviews  Pictures  Videos  Community
Snapshots of your day-to-day life.
Those are really crucial, you know.
Mm-hmm.
Is this me cleaning the stain here?
Here is Kinme-san, the owner of Kinme Cleaning, treating a
stain on a customer's garment! She works very carefully,
applying a series of detergents to safely remove the stain.
Of course!
Comment
Like
Share
What a great shot. I'm impressed!
So does that mean it's done,
and we don't have to do anything else?
No, this is just the beginning.
First, we need to get more followers.
Followers?
Right here. It's like the number
of fans you have.
When the number gets bigger, it means
more people are watching your account.
Write a Comment
Community
0 People Have Liked This Page
0 People Are Following This Page
Basic Info
View All
Address
______ 1-2-3, Atami, Shizuoka Prefecture
Category
Cleaning
Rating
View All
has no reviews
Reviews: 0
Send a Message
View All
It's still at zero right now, though.
I hope we get more soon.
We'll keep updating the page regularly.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
Thank you very much. But don't
spend too much time on it, okay?
Okay!
Um, Aji-san?
Hmm? What's up?
I got someone to make an account for
the shop on the internet a few days ago.
Would you mind taking a look
when you get a chance?
What the heck is that?
Some kind of TV show?
Ah, not exactly. Um...
I can't explain it well myself.
Why don't you try asking me
again once you can?
I guess you're right.
A lot of my customers here
are elderly, after all.
Community
8 People Have Liked This Page
7 People Are Following This Page
You still aren't getting
a lot of followers yet.
The only people following are
the salesman and people he knows.
Well, maybe that's just the way it goes.
I thought you'd have a lot more by now.
Oh, it's fine. There's no rush.
Customer service work is never
that easy to begin with.
Try not to let it bother you too much.
I have a delivery!
Oh! All right!
A package?
Something for the shop
from another prefecture?
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
"To Kinme-sama of Kinme Cleaning,
I sent this after seeing
your Facenote page.
No other cleaner would accept it.
Do you think you can take care of this?"
Huh?
What?
Wash It All Away
Wow, so you started a Facenote page?
Yes. Do you have a Face...
Um, do you have one of those too?
Nah, too much of a hassle for me.
I'd rather keep my social life simple.
But as busy you are, do you
have time to keep it updated?
Yes, well...
I don't really understand
the social... media yet,
so I have some schoolgirls from
the neighborhood helping me out.
Schoolgirls from the neighborhood?
Who could that be?
Huh?
Never mind.
So, are you seeing results?
Yes, I am. Someone already mailed me
an item to clean from another town.
What? That's great!
It's just, I wasn't expecting it at all,
so it was kind of a surprise.
This one was in a condition
I could work with,
but I'm afraid I'll also get requests
that are beyond my abilities.
Yeah, I can see that.
If people sent you an item out of the blue
and complained when you decline,
that wouldn't be much fun.
You're right.
But I do find myself checking online
recommendations a lot these days.
Especially for doctors and dentists.
Recommendations...
You can't always expect word of mouth
to be accurate, though.
Especially for restaurant reviews.
Do you... pay attention to those?
Hey, don't worry.
Even if there are cleaners out there
with a better reputation,
I'll always come to you instead.
Thank you very much.
But if you do start getting busy
with online orders,
maybe you won't need to wash things
for us locals anymore.
N-No, that would never happen!
I'm just kidding!
See you!
Thank you very much.
Recommendations, huh?
Kinme-oneesan!
Huh? Nairo-chan?
Your account is...
b-blowing up right now!
What?
Community
2,402 People Have Liked This Page
2,366 People Are Following This Page
Take a look at this!
Huh?
Two thousand?!
H-How did I get so many?
It looks like it started with
the person from before.
Person from before?
This hat holds a lot of memories for me.
It actually got so dirty that cleaners
wouldn't even touch it, but then I decided
to try my luck with a shop I found
on Facenote. I had honestly given up,
but look at it now.
The work was done by an independent
shop in Atami called Kinme Cleaning.
I'm so glad that they were able to clean it!
OMU RAOO  Wow! It looks brand new!
ra1112 I have a cardigan that I've kept
locked away because it's so badly
stained. Does this Kinme Cleaning
accept online orders? Maybe I should
give them a try too.
2759 Likes
Oh! It's that hat!
This lady is actually a famous influencer!
Her name is Maleko.
Influencer?
A kind of online celebrity
that a lot of people listen to.
This hat holds a lot of memories for me.
It actually got so dirty that cleaners
wouldn't even touch it, but then I decided
to try my luck with a shop I found
on Facenote. I had honestly given up,
but look at it now.
The work was done by an independent
shop in Atami called Kinme Cleaning.
I'm so glad that they were able to clean it!
When this lady recommended your shop,
you got a bunch of new followers!
Hello, this is Kinme Cleaning.
Yes. So not a pick-up, but a mail order?
What? From Hokkaido?!
Are these all orders?
I'll have to check everything inside
and get back to the owners.
Hello, this is Kinme Cleaning.
What?! You want to send an item from Saga?
I apologize for being so late today.
Don't worry about it, dear.
Any time is fine with me.
I'm telling ya, man, real angels exist.
Yeah, right.
No way, man.
Oh! Kinme-san!
Good afternoon, Moruda-kun.
Oh, is that her?
Wow.
I know, right? I told you she was pretty!
Huh?
But wow, Kinme-san!
You actually got to clean Maleko's hat!
Huh? How did you know about that?
I've been following Maleko for a while.
She is an angel.
Yeah.
I believe it now.
But I mean, I didn't even know
you were on Facenote.
Yeah.
Uh, yes.
I just followed you too!
She's the real thing. Insane!
Hey, guys! You better not go bragging
on Facenote that you met Kinme-san!
The internet is incredible.
It's okay if you say you met
my true older sister, though.
What are you talking about?
I am very sorry, but I am buried in orders
right now, so it may take extra time.
Yes, one or two days would be difficult.
I'm very sorry.
Hello, this is Kinme Cleaning.
What? A pick-up in Yokohama?
I'm very sorry, but I must decline.
Yes. Please accept my apologies.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Got some packages for you.
A whole bunch today.
Huh?!
Vacancies
Yadoya's Thoughts
I hurt my back as soon as I
got up this morning.
I couldn't move for 30 minutes.
This street has a lot more
trendy shops now than it used to.
Lots of, what's the word, renovations?
Maybe I should update too.
Kyusho-kun...
Huh?
K-Kinme-san!
I'm so glad I caught you!
I saw you at the shop,
but you turned around and left.
Huh? Oh... yeah.
Moruda had already warned me, but you
looked even busier than I expected.
So I figured it could wait.
No, it can't!
Huh?
It can't wait.
Because...
you requested this quite a while ago,
so your bag takes priority.
Kinme-san.
Yes?
Did you mean to keep your apron on
when you left the shop?
Uh...
No, I didn't! I didn't even realize!
But I was in such a rush...
Okay, then. Please take care of my bag.
Sure!
You can count on Kinme!
Translation:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michael Arnold
Ashley Barboza
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Riley Dalton
Sriram Gurunathan
Oh, look at that! Just as I expected.
She's very popular!
I'm glad I recommended that she try it.
But if she leverages her assets even more,
she'll really shine!
Episode 8  That Was Too Impressive
Next time is "That Was Too Impressive."